export const Questions = [
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: "How many kids does Stephen want to have?",
    correctAnswer: "8",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "2",
      "3",
      "6"
    ]
  },

  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: "What is Stephen's favorite color?",
    correctAnswer: "Blue",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Orange",
      "Red",
      "Green"
    ]
  },

  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: "Who is Stephen's favorite co-worker?",
    correctAnswer: "Humphries",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Ben 2",
      "Andrew",
      "Nick"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: "What apartment complex does Stephen live at?",
    correctAnswer: "Glenwood",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "King Henry",
      "Heritage",
      "Condo Row"
    ]
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: "What is Stephen's favorite movie?",
    correctAnswer: "Inception",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Tenet",
      "Dark Knight",
      "Interstellar"
    ]
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: "What is the name of Stephen's ex-girlfriend?",
    correctAnswer: "Kate",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Lizzy",
      "Lexi",
      "Emma"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: "What is Stephen's favorite book series?",
    correctAnswer: "Percy Jackson",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Harry Potter",
      "The Hunger Games",
      "The Chronicles of Narnia"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: "What is Stephen's favorite scripture?",
    correctAnswer: "Doctrine and Covenants 10:5",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Ether 12:27",
      "2nd Nephi 5:27",
      "Isaiah 1:13"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: "What is Stephen's favorite College Football team?",
    correctAnswer: "Utah",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Arizona",
      "Texas",
      "BYU"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: "What State has Stephen not lived in?",
    correctAnswer: "Florida",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "California",
      "Washington",
      "Colorado"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: "When will Stephen get married?",
    correctAnswer: "Next time a girl says they like him",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "Never",
      "When he graduates",
      "On his 25th birthday"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: "How many girls has Stephen kissed?",
    correctAnswer: "2",
    wrongAnswers: [
      "0",
      "1",
      "8"
    ]
  },
]

export const topics = [
  "Biology",
  "Maths",
  "English",
  "History",
]
